

LUONG THANH QUANG

INTERN FRONT END

PERSONAL INFORMATION

- 0949699222
- quang20042204@gmail.com
- 1 https://quang2204.github.io/Portfolio
- Minh Khai Bac Tu Liem Hanoi

SKILLS

BACKEND

- Php
- RESTful APi

FRONT END

- HTML5/CSS3 Sass
- JavaScript
- ReactJS Redux Thunk
- Tailwindcss , Bootstrap

DATABASE

•MySQL - SQLSever

INTEREST

Exercise, Read a book

INTRODUCE

A final year student majoring in Information Technology at FPT College, I am passionate about learning and developing programming skills. I have experience working with languages such as Html,Css,Javascript,Reactjs,Php. I have participated in many group and individual projects related to website development. Good communication skills and the ability to work independently as well as in a team help me confidently apply for an IT internship position at the company. I look forward to having the opportunity to learn and contribute to real projects.

CAREER GOALS

Short-term goals (1 month - 3 months)

- · Complete the company's training program and participate in real projects
- Become an official employee of the company
- To apply my educational background in Information Technology by contributing to software development projects at the company, enhancing both my coding and problem-solving skills

Long-term goals (> 2 years)

- Become a Fullstack programmer
- Wish to contribute more to the company and possibly become a Leader of any team to help the company develop sustainably
- · Wish to become the person in charge of the company's main projects

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE IT DEVELOPER

06/10/2023 - Now

Project: Developing e-commerce website

Customer: A person online

• Implementation time: November 2023 - December 2023

Describe project:

 The project aims to build an e-commerce website with online product buying and selling functions.

Technology and techniques used :

- Programming languages: Html5, Css3, JavaScript
- · Tools and framework: Bootstrap

Development skills:

- Professional skills: Front-end development with Html5, Css3, JavaScript, Bootstrap.
- Soft skills: Effective time management, communicating with customers via email and online meetings via meet.

Results and achievements

- Complete the project 2 weeks ahead of schedule.
- · Website operates stably.
- Customers highly appreciate communication ability and professionalism during the working process.
- Website link: https://quang2204.github.io/shophoaqua/

EDUCATION

PROFESSIONAL / WEB PROGRAMMING

9-2022 - Now

FPT POLYTEACHNIC COLLEGE

Period students 5: GPA 8.5/10

LANGUAGE

English reading comprehension

SOFT SKILLS

Office

Word, exel, powerpoint

Presentation - Group work

Ability to quickly learn and become familiar with new technologies

PROJECT

LEADER

WEBSITE SELLING CLOTHES 01/2024 - 04/2024

Practical project at school: Project 1

Project includes: 1 person

Bootstrap 5, Html5/Css3, Php/Laragon, Tailwindcss, Ajax

Use Bootstrap 5, tailwindcss and Html5 to design the interface

- Laragon to design and manage the database
- · Php performs functions such as purchasing, registering, logging in, paying...
- · Ajax so that when a small change is needed, there is no need to reload the entire website

Location:

• Project management of database design, interface design, implementation of user-side data dumping and user-side functions, Crud admin page, Online payment

Link website: https://github.com/quang2204/duan.git

LEADER

WEBSITE QUIZZ GAME 05/2024 - 06/2024

Practical project at school: Project 2

Project includes: 1 person

Bootstrap 5, Html5 / Css3, Php / Laragon, Tailwindcss, Ajax

Use Bootstrap 5, tailwindcss and Html5 to design the interface

- Use Bootstrap 5, Tailwind CSS and HTML5 to design the user interface.
- · ReactJS performs functions such as taking quizzes, registering, and logging in
- · Manage application state efficiently and predictably with Redux, integrating with ReactJS to build complex, dynamic web applications

Location:

- User Interface: "Use Bootstrap 5, Tailwind CSS, and HTML5 to design beautiful and responsive interfaces."
- · Database management:
- · Application logic and functions:
- Use ReactJS and Redux to manage state and perform functions like creating questions, tracking scores, logging in, and registering players

Link git: https://github.com/quang2204/Quizizz